Harrison Gerry

3 Wellington Road, Hampton Hill, TW12 1JP (+44) 07526 890577 | h3gerry@googlemail.com GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

Personal Profile

I have had a long standing interest in technology. As an avid gamer I have interacted with many who also share this passion and this is what drew me into learning how to code. I have always wanted to understand how the programs that are so deeply integrated into our lives and how they can be improved upon into the future.

I have recently finished a software development bootcamp that has taught me essential concepts of coding. I have enjoyed learning how to algorithmically solve problems and utilizing the tools provided by programming languages. I work well in teams and am a confident communicator.

I look forward to entering my first role in the field and gaining an understanding of the various specializations available to me. I am excited about its constantly evolving nature with many challenges to solve.

Education

11/2023 - 02/2024 | Software development course, Just IT Training Ltd, London Digital Skills Bootcamp: Software Development A twelve week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of Web and Software development.

07/2018 - 08/2020 | NPL (provided by CSR group), Teddington, Greater London BTEC Level 3 Diploma: Applied Science (Merit, Merit) Level 3 Laboratory Technician Standard

07/2012 - 06/2017 | Teddington School, Greater London GCSEs: 9 GCSEs including Maths (7), Physics (A), Biology (A)

IT Skills

Software Development Skills: GitHub - MS Teams

Web Technology: HTML - CSS

Core Programming Languages: Python - JavaScript - MySQL

Projects:

- A program using JavaScript that facilitates easy creation of JS objects
- An application using python and MySQL that tracks ingredients and allows easy access to potion making for use in tabletop role playing games

Employment History

04/2022-11/2023 Boethius Boffee Ltd, London - Barista

- Serving up to 120 customers a day and providing a comfortable and efficient service.
- Working with colleagues with clear communication to ensure that orders were delivered in a timely and correct manner.
- Covered for colleagues who were unable to work to prevent staff shortage.

03/2021 - 12/2021 UCB, Slough - Analytical scientist

- Careful cataloging test results gained from sensitive and unique samples.
- Following procedure in order to get repeatable and consistent results.
- Working as a team on an under budgeted project to produce results under strict time constraints.
- Analyzing errors on equipment and referencing the documentation to find the correct way forwards.

07/2018 - 08/2020 National Physical Laboratory, Location - Junior research scientist

- Ordering stock to ensure that testing operations run smoothly.
- Being responsible for sensitive and expensive laboratory equipment and materials.
- Working on a project from the perspective of a user who is unfamiliar with a product and providing feedback on its usability. The customer was pleased with the result.

Interests and Achievements

I built my own gaming PC to run highly modified games.

I spend time in communities that have a high proportion of developers, security specialists and people involved in devops.

I play in an in person roleplaying game weekly (Dungeons and Dragons) where a team and I work together to overcome challenges laid out before us by the Game master. These challenges range from puzzles to tactical combat to solving political disputes.

I test my friends' games to find softlocks, visual bugs and poor balance. I then record the scenario and steps leading up to the bug in order to provide them the best chance of squashing the bug.